horoscopes-love.eu 2016-11-28

# Privacy Policy

     Last Updated on December 03, 2015 
     Written by admin 

We respect your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at our site The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

  What information do we collect?

  We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..  
What do we use your information for? 

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:   
; To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)  
; To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)  
; To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature  
; To send periodic emails

> The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

Log Files   

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Cookies    

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. 

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.  

Links       
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

    Advertisers    

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. We work with the ad companies: Google Adsense. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies. 

    Contact Information    

 If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.    

Dart cookie:

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Because publisher sites and laws across countries vary, we're unable to suggest specific privacy policy language. However, you may wish to review resources such as the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/), or NAI, which suggests the following language for data collection of non-personally identifying information:

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Contacting Us  

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

www.horoscopes-love.eu            [info@horoscopes-love.eu](mailto:info@horoscopes-love.eu) 

Share this post:

Love in 2017?

When will I find love? What does 2017 Year hold for you? How to find a soulmate? Chat with free tested experts. Ask them now! [Click here ](http://www.oranum.com/chat/random-expert?s=1&p=6&w=100393&t=216&c=5961)

Need answers?

Love, relationship, finance, family, career and health problems? Visit portal with free chat that connects you with the world's most renowned Psychics. [Click here ](http://www.oranum.com/randomchat.php?s=1&p=6&w=100393&t=36&c=5961)
